(Raj:)Mm.
Gentlemen, I put it to you:
(Raj:)The worst tapioca pudding...
(Raj:)...is better than the best pudding
of any other flavor.
(Sheldon:)First off, that is axiomatically wrong
because the best pudding is chocolate.
(Sheldon:)Secondly, the organic structure of tapioca
makes it a jiggling bowl of potential death.
(Sheldon:)- It is extracted from the plant...
- Hey, I'm thinking of growing a mustache.
Oh, no kidding.
- A Fu Manchu, a handlebar, pencil?
- It's extracted from...
(Howard:)I'm not sure yet.
You know, George Clooney has one now.
(Raj:)Really? I once saw him
shopping at Ralphs.
(Raj:)He was buying tequila.
Wow, you'd think a guy like that
would have some kind of booze lackey.
All right, this is cruel.
(Leonard:)We better let him finish
before his head explodes.
All right. Sheldon, why is tapioca...?
(Sheldon:)Tapioca is extracted
from the root of Manihot esculenta.
(Sheldon:)Due to a high concentration of cyanide...
(Sheldon:)...it is poisonous in its raw form
and lethal if prepared improperly.